A Guide to the Typography Ephemera Collection, 1842, 1883-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- The Stagecoach Press 1956-1960 (Box-folder 16:22)
- Stamperia del Stantuccio 1950 (Box-folder 16:23)
- Standard, Paul 1947 (Box-folder 16:24)
- State University of Iowa 1948 (Box-folder 16:25)
- Stechert-Hafner 1954 (Box-folder 16:26)
- Stempel Type Founders n.d. (Box-folder 16:27)
- Stephenson Blake n.d. (Box-folder 16:28)
- Stephenson Blake n.d. (Box-folder 17:1)
- Still Point Press n.d. (Box-folder 17:2)
- The Stinehour Press 1958-1967 (Box-folder 17:3)
- Stone, Edward L. 1931-1933 (Box-folder 17:4)
- Stonehouse Press 1983-1988 (Box-folder 17:5)
- The Stratford Book 1946-1947 (Box-folder 17:6)
- The Stratford Press 1953, 1960 (Box-folder 17:7)
- Sub Rosa Press n.d. (Box-folder 17:8)
- Sumac Press 1947-1960 (Box-folder 17:9)
- Superior Type Founder's Company 1934 (Box-folder 17:10)
- Swap Circ 1961 (Box-folder 17:11)
- Swink, S. S. 1951 (Box-folder 17:12)
- Syracuse University Press n.d. (Box-folder 17:13)
- T.J. Lyons Press 1959 (Box-folder 17:14)
- Talisman Press 1962 (Box-folder 17:15)
- Talmud Publishing Company n.d. (Box-folder 17:16)
- Tamal Land Press 1974 (Box-folder 17:17)
- Tamalpais Press 1958-1968 (Box-folder 17:18)
- Tasmanian Historical Research Association 1965 (Box-folder 17:19)
- Tauser Head Press 1965 (Box-folder 17:20)
- Taylor, W. Thomas 1983-1987 (Box-folder 17:21)
- Tenfingers Press 1967, 1973 (Box-folder 17:22)
- Tern Press n.d. (Box-folder 17:23)
- Thee Hellbox Press 1986 (Box-folder 17:24)
- James Thin 1948 (Box-folder 17:25)
- The Thistle Press 1953, 1961 (Box-folder 17:26)
- Thomajan, P. K. 1952 (Box-folder 17:27)
- Thornily, Bill n.d. (Box-folder 17:28)
- The Tidal Press 1986 (Box-folder 18:1)
- The Tideline Press 1984 (Box-folder 18:2)
- Tommasini, A. R. (small booklets sent as Christmas wishes) 1953-1963 (Box-folder 18:3)
- Toothpaste Press 1978-1980 (Box-folder 18:4)
- Trovillion Private Press 1958-1961 (Box-folder 18:5)
- Trianon Press 1959-1960 (Box-folder 18:6)
- Truex Press 1977 (Box-folder 18:7)
- Turkey Press 1983-1987 (Box-folder 18:8)
- Turtle Island Press n.d. (Box-folder 18:9)
- Two Pears Press 1981 (Box-folder 18:10)
- Twowindows Press n.d. (Box-folder 18:11)
- Type Design (Falcon: Designed by W.A. Dwiggins) 1962 (Box-folder 18:12)
- Type Design / or Designers 1947-1961 (Box-folder 18:13)
- Type - Steve L. Watts. Front Royal, Virginia 1958 (Box-folder 18:14)
- Type Directors Club 1953-1971 (Box-folder 18:15)
- Type Foundry "Amsterdam" n.d. (Box-folder 18:16)
- The Type Shop n.d. (Box-folder 18:17)
- Typographer's Digest 1959-1960 (Box-folder 18:18)
- The Typographical Widow 1948 (Box-folder 18:19)
- Typography 1948 (Box-folder 18:20)
- Typophiles 1935-1982 (Box-folder 18:21)
- Typothetae Federation 1923 (Box-folder 19:1)
- Ueberreuter - Rosenbaum, Wien 1981 (Box-folder 19:2)
- Underfoot Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:3)
- The Underground Press 1956 (Box-folder 19:4)
- United Efforts Press 1961 (Box-folder 19:5)
- United States Government Printing Office 1956 (Box-folder 19:6)
- United Typothetae of America 1933 (Box-folder 19:7)
- University of California Press 1953, 1984 (Box-folder 19:8)
- University of Chicago Press 1964 (Box-folder 19:9)
- University of Kentucky Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:10)
- University of Nebraska, Omaha 1981 (Box-folder 19:11)
- University of Texas- Austin Texas n.d. (Box-folder 19:12)
- Updike, Daniel Beverly 1941 (Box-folder 19:13)
- The Upstairs Press 1981 (Box-folder 19:14)
- Vagabond Hand Bookbindery 1983 (Box-folder 19:15)
- The Vagabond Press 1961-1981 (Box-folder 19:16)
- Valenti Angelo Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:17)
- Vial, Yves 1984 (Box-folder 19:18)
- Victoria Platen Press 1981 (Box-folder 19:19)
- Ward Ritchie Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:20)
- Warwick Press 1978 (Box-folder 19:21)
- Wayside Press 1945 (Box-folder 19:22)
- Weber, C.E. n.d. (Box-folder 19:23)
- Wells, James and Elizabeth, Printers 1936 (Box-folder 19:24)
- Wesleyan University Press 1960 (Box-folder 19:25)
- Westvaco 1926 (Box-folder 19:26)
- Whelwick Press 1956 (Box-folder 19:27)
- Whipporwill Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:28)
- Whittington Press 1977 (Box-folder 19:29)
- William Andrews Clark Memorial Library 1980 (Box-folder 19:30)
- William Byrd Press 1958 (Box-folder 19:31)
- William E. Rudge's Sons 1953 (Box-folder 19:32)
- William Morris Society 1956-1966 (Box-folder 19:33)
- Williamsburg Press 1973 (Box-folder 19:34)
- Wilmac Press 1961 (Box-folder 19:35)
- Wilson, Adrian 1980 (Box-folder 19:36)
- Wm. J. Keller Inc. 1953 (Box-folder 19:37)
- Wind River Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:38)
- The Windsor Press 1928 (Box-folder 19:39)
- Woodblocks - Use of in Illustrations n.d. (Box-folder 19:40)
- Wrappers - "Printed Wrappers of the Fifteenth to the Eighteenth Centuries" 1952 (Box-folder 19:41)
- Wreden, William P. 1975 (Box-folder 19:42)
- Wrongtree Press n.d. (Box-folder 19:43)
- Yale University Press 1958 (Box-folder 19:44)
- Yolla Bolly Press 1983-1987 (Box-folder 19:45)
- Zanella, Alessandro 1989 (Box-folder 19:46)
- Zapf, Hermann n.d. (Box-folder 19:47)
- Zeitlin and Ver Brugge 1950 (Box-folder 19:48)